

RENDI PURNOMO

 $08995232430 \ | \ rendipurnomo \ | \ https://www.linkedin.com/in/rendipurnomo \ | \ https://github.com/rendipurnomo \ | \ https://github.com/ren$

Karanganyar

I have experience as a Graphic Designer at Dua Naga Onpreneur. has been familiar with creating content for various social media platforms. proven to have increased 30% of sales on the social media accounts that I manage. and now I have an interest in web development by following bootcamp.

Work Experiences

Dua Naga Onpreneur - Sukoharjo

Jul 2022 - Sep 2022

Design Grafis

Ad Agency

• Contribute to increase 30% of sales through social media platforms

PT.Hailai - Surakarta

Jan 2022 - Aug 2022

Mechanical Engineering

- · Lead a team of 2 fulltime employees
- Contribute to reducing 50% of building maintenance cost

PT. Estetika Joglo Utama - Surakarta

Jun 2019 - Feb 2021

General Affair

Aestetic Clinic

- Contribute to reducing the building maintenance budget by 25% by maximizing preventive maintenance.
- · Fully responsible for building maintenance, company assets, clinic licensing, and coordinating OB and security

PT.Pama PersadaNusantara - Jakarta

Jun 2010 - Dec 2015

Site Support Equipment Mechanic

Coal Contractor

- Responsible for maintaining and repairing heavy equipment and supporting tools for coal production with KPI readiness units of more than 80%.
- Contribute to the Best mechanic competition in 2014

Education Level

HariSenin.com - Jakarta Certificate in Full Stack Development Bootcamp	Aug 2022 - Oct 2022
Udemy · Certificate in Web Development Bootcamp	Aug 2022 - Oct 2022
SMK Warga · - Surakarta	Jun 2007 - Jun 2010

Organisational Experience

BumDes - Karanganyar

Sep 2018 - Nov 2019

Operation Supervisor

Badan Usaha Milik Desa

- · Provide assistance in managing BumDes.
- Conduct research on village-owned businesses in collaboration with relevant stakeholders.

Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- Soft Skills (2012): leadership dan teamwork
- Soft Skills : Problem Solving
- Hard Skills (2022): Web Developer
- Modules Taken (2022): Javascript, react, Next